lechateau.com 2018-09-06

# LE CHÂTEAU

### LE CHÂTEAU'S PRIVACY POLICY

##### Updated: February 14, 2014

We at LE CHÂTEAU Inc. respect your privacy. This privacy policy (the "Policy") describes the manner in which we collect your personal information and how we treat it consistent with our commitment to providing you with a satisfying and helpful shopping experience.

By using the www.lechateau.com website and/or making an online purchase of products, you agree to the terms and conditions of the Policy and as it may be updated from time to time. Accordingly, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the top of this page) and review any changes since the last version.

#### What is Personal Information?

Personal Information is virtually any information that refers to an individual specifically and is recorded in any form. Personal information includes such things as age, income, date of birth, email and postal addresses, telephone numbers and financial information.

#### How is Personal Information collected?

Personal Information is collected online by us when users voluntarily register with us to purchase items, receive electronic newsletters, emails, use communication services, answer surveys and enter contests or other promotional opportunities and when users make a purchase.

www.lechateau.com is designed for use by adults. LE CHÂTEAU does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. Those under age 13 should not use LE CHÂTEAU's website or provide LE CHÂTEAU with any personal information.

#### 1\. PURPOSE OF COLLECTION

We use Personal Information in an effort to improve your shopping experience, to communicate with you about our products, promotions or contests, if any, to protect you and us from error and fraud, to process your requests or orders and to keep track of transactions and to comply with legal and governmental requirements. We may also use this information to make offers to you, to help us target specific products to you, and to help us develop and improve our Site and tailor it to your interests.

#### 2\. CONSENT

We will collect, use or disclose your Personal Information only with your knowledge and consent, except where required or permitted by law.

You may withdraw your consent at any time, on reasonable notice, subject to legal or contractual restrictions. LE CHÂTEAU will inform you of the implications of doing so. To amend your consent, refer to the [Contact Us](https://www.lechateau.com/style/company/links/contacUs.jsp) section.

#### 3\. LIMITING USE, DISCLOSURE, AND RETENTION

Personal information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or permitted by law. It will be retained only as long as necessary for these purposes or as required by law.

We support the Do Not Track browser setting. Do Not Track (or DNT) is a preference you can set in your browser to let the websites you visit know that you do not want them collecting certain information about you.

#### 4\. ACCURACY

We will keep your Personal Information as accurate, complete and up-to-date as necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used. You may request access to your Personal Information we have on record in order to review and amend the information, as appropriate. In circumstances where your Personal Information has been provided by a third party, we will refer you to that party (e.g., credit bureaus).

#### 5\. SAFEGUARDS AND ACCOUNTABILITY

LE CHÂTEAU will protect Personal Information by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information, including through the use of the following measures: (i) physical security measures, such as restricted access facilities and appropriate disposal of Personal Information; and (ii) electronic security measures, such as password protection, for accessing computerized Personal Information.

LE CHÂTEAU is responsible for Personal Information under its control, including any Personal Information that is transferred to third parties for processing, storage or other purposes.

When we use trusted third parties to act on our behalf by performing such functions as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, processing credit card payments or providing customer service, contractual or other appropriate means are used to ensure compliance by such third parties with this Policy and all applicable privacy laws.

#### 6\. OPENNESS AND INDIVIDUAL ACCESS

This Policy and any related information is available at all times on our web site, www.lechateau.com under this Privacy Policy or on request.

Upon request, LE CHÂTEAU will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of Personal Information relating to you, and give you access to that information. You have the right to challenge the accuracy and completeness of your information and have it amended as appropriate.

#### 7\. CONTACTING US

For anything to do with this Policy, including questions, comments, withdrawing consent or to challenge our compliance with this Policy, please submit your inquiry using the [Contact Us](https://www.lechateau.com/style/company/links/contacUs.jsp) area of our web site.

LE CHÂTEAU will inform individuals who make inquiries or lodge complaints about its inquiry or complaint procedures, as applicable. If a complaint is found to be justified, we will take appropriate measures, including, if necessary, amending our policies and practices.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small text files which embed themselves on your hard drive from some of the Site's pages. Cookies are harmless in the sense that they cannot extract any information from your hard drive, over which you have complete control. LE CHÂTEAU uses Cookies to determine site traffic, convey useful information about your interests, and to personalize any future visits you make to the Site. Cookies do not systematically provide LE CHÂTEAU with any personal information about you, and you can opt to stop receiving Cookies at any time by simply modifying your browser's configuration.

#### Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to sites other than our own. Those sites may have their own privacy policy, or no privacy policy at all. We are not responsible for those sites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience of our visitors. These sites may send their own cookies to you and may collect information and use it in a way inconsistent with this Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third-party sites or services before providing any of them with any of your Personal Information. LE CHÂTEAU does not control the content that appears on these sites or take any responsibility for their content, nor should it be implied that LE CHÂTEAU endorses or otherwise recommends such sites or their products or services offered.
